Office of Institutional Research and Evaluation Records UA042
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Surveys and reports, 1900 -- 2007; 1965 -- 1999; UA042.001; 56.4 Linear Feet; 139 Digital Object(s)
  - HEDS Senior Survey, 1998; UA042.001.036.00008; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Senior Survey Comparison, 1999; UA042.001.036.00009; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Enrollment, 1974 -- 1978; UA042.001.036.00010; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Enrollment, 1960 -- 1985; UA042.001.036.00011; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Enrollment, 1981 -- 1992; UA042.001.036.00012; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Enrollment- IPEDS, 1988; UA042.001.036.00013; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Enrollment- IPEDS, 1989; UA042.001.036.00014; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Enrollment- IPEDS, 1991; UA042.001.036.00015; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Enrollment, 1992; UA042.001.036.00016; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Enrollment, 1993; UA042.001.036.00017; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Enrollment, 1994; UA042.001.036.00018; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Enrollment - IPEDS, 1995; UA042.001.036.00019; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Enrollment - IPEDS, 1996 -- 2004; UA042.001.036.00020; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
    - Enrollment 96, 2004; UA042.001.036.00020.00001; Office of Institutional Research
  - Enrollment - IPEDS, 1997; UA042.001.036.00021; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Enrollment - IPEDS, 1999; UA042.001.036.00022; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
    - ip99.xls, 1999; UA042.001.036.00022.00001; Office of Institutional Research
  - Fall Staff, 1993; UA042.001.036.00023; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Fall Staff Survey, 1995; UA042.001.036.00024; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Fall Staff Survey, 1997; UA042.001.036.00025; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Finance IPEDS, 1985 -- 1990; UA042.001.036.00026; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Finance IPEDS, 1987 -- 1988; UA042.001.036.00027; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Finance IPEDS, 1991; UA042.001.036.00028; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Finance IPEDS, 1992; UA042.001.036.00029; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Finance IPEDS, 1993; UA042.001.036.00030; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Finance IPEDS, 1994; UA042.001.036.00031; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Finance IPEDS 94/1995, 1994 -- 1995; UA042.001.036.00032; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Finance IPEDS, 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.036.00033; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Finance IPEDS, 1996 -- 1997; UA042.001.036.00034; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Finance IPEDS, 1997 -- 1998; UA042.001.036.00035; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Finance IPEDS, 1997 -- 1998; UA042.001.036.00036; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Finance IPEDS, 1998; UA042.001.036.00037; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Library IPEDS, 1992; UA042.001.036.00038; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Library IPEDS, 1994 -- 2004; UA042.001.036.00039; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
    - IPEDS Lib94, 2004; UA042.001.036.00039.00001; Office of Institutional Research
  - Library IPEDS, 1996; UA042.001.036.00040; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
    - Library 1996, UA042.001.036.00040.00001; Office of Institutional Research
  - Library IPEDS, 1998; UA042.001.036.00041; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
    - Library 98, 1998; UA042.001.036.00041.00001; Office of Institutional Research
  - Staff IPEDS, 1983 -- 1985; UA042.001.036.00042; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Reports Issued [1 of 5], 1990; UA042.001.036.00043; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Reports Issued [2 of 5], 1990; UA042.001.036.00044; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Reports Issued [3 of 5], 1990; UA042.001.036.00045; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Reports Issued [4 of 5], 1990; UA042.001.036.00046; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - Reports Issued [5 of 5], 1990; UA042.001.036.00047; Office of Institutional Research (Box 36)
  - HEDS Reports Issued [1 of 4], 1993; UA042.001.037.00001; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - HEDS Reports Issued [2 of 4], 1993; UA042.001.037.00002; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - HEDS Reports Issued [3 of 4], 1993; UA042.001.037.00003; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - HEDS Reports Issued [4 of 4], 1993; UA042.001.037.00004; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - HEDS Reports Issued (non-numbered) [1 of 2], 1993; UA042.001.037.00005; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - HEDS Reports Issued (non-numbered) [2 of 2], 1993; UA042.001.037.00006; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - HEDS Reports Issued 1988A [1 of 3], UA042.001.037.00007; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - HEDS Reports Issued 1988A [2 of 3], UA042.001.037.00008; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - HEDS Reports Issued 1988A [3 of 3], UA042.001.037.00009; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - HEDS Reports Issued [1 of 4], 1989; UA042.001.037.00010; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - HEDS Reports Issued [2 of 4], 1989; UA042.001.037.00011; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - HEDS Reports Issued [3 of 4], 1989; UA042.001.037.00012; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - HEDS Reports Issued [4 of 4], 1989; UA042.001.037.00013; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - Reports Issued Book 1 [1 of 3], 1989; UA042.001.037.00014; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - Reports Issued Book 1 [2 of 3], 1989; UA042.001.037.00015; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - Reports Issued Book 1 [3 of 3], 1989; UA042.001.037.00016; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - IPEDS - Institutional characteristics survey, 1994 -- 1995; UA042.001.037.00017; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - IPEDS - Institutional characteristics survey, 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.037.00018; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - IPEDS - Institutional characteristics survey, 1996 -- 1997; UA042.001.037.00019; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - IPEDS - Institutional characteristics survey, 1997 -- 1998; UA042.001.037.00020; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - IPEDS - Institutional characteristics survey, 1998 -- 1999; UA042.001.037.00021; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - IPEDS - Salaries, Tenure, and Fringe Benefits of Full-time Instructional Faculty Survey, 1993 -- 1994; UA042.001.037.00022; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - IPEDS - Salaries, Tenure, and Fringe Benefits of Full-time Instructional Faculty Survey, 1994 -- 1995; UA042.001.037.00023; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - IPEDS - Salaries, Tenure, and Fringe Benefits of Full-time Instructional Faculty Survey, 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.037.00024; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
    - IPEDS - FacSal Iped95.wk4, 1995; UA042.001.037.00024.00001; Office of Institutional Research
  - IPEDS - Salaries, Tenure, and Fringe Benefits of Full-time Instructional Faculty Survey, 1996 -- 1997; UA042.001.037.00025; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
    - SA168148.txt / Ipeds96.wk4, 1996 -- 1997; UA042.001.037.00025.00001; Office of Institutional Research
  - IPEDS - Salaries, Tenure, and Fringe Benefits of Full-time Instructional Faculty Survey, 1997 -- 1998; UA042.001.037.00026; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
    - Ipedf.wk4, 1997 -- 1998; UA042.001.037.00026.00001; Office of Institutional Research
  - IPEDS - Salaries, Tenure, and Fringe Benefits of Full-time Instructional Faculty Survey, 1998 -- 1999; UA042.001.037.00027; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - Telecom Service Requests and Costs, 1991 -- 1995; UA042.001.037.00028; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - Travel Expenses, 1994; UA042.001.037.00029; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - Pre-Major Advising Survey, 2000; UA042.001.037.00030; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - Sophomore Experience Report, 2001; UA042.001.037.00031; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - Senior Survey, 2006; UA042.001.037.00032; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - Sophomore Experience and First Year Engineering Advising Survey PREVIEW, 2001; UA042.001.037.00033; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - Sophomore Survey [1 of 2], 2002; UA042.001.037.00034; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - Sophomore Survey [2 of 2], 2002; UA042.001.037.00035; Office of Institutional Research (Box 37)
  - Sophomore Experience Survey for Engineering Students, 2003; UA042.001.038.00001; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Pre-Major Advising and Sophomore Experience Survey for Liberal Arts Students [1 of 3], 2003; UA042.001.038.00002; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Pre-Major Advising and Sophomore Experience Survey for Liberal Arts Students [2 of 3], 2003; UA042.001.038.00003; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Pre-Major Advising and Sophomore Experience Survey for Liberal Arts Students [3 of 3], 2003; UA042.001.038.00004; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Sophomore Experience Survey, 2004; UA042.001.038.00005; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Alum, 1991; UA042.001.038.00006; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Baccalaureate Origins of Doctorate Recipients, 1988 -- 1991; UA042.001.038.00007; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Comparisons with Peer Institutions Class of, 1995; UA042.001.038.00008; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - HEDS Alumni Survey, 1991; UA042.001.038.00009; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Senior Survey HEDS/COFHE Comparisons, 1995; UA042.001.038.00010; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Tuition and Fees, 1986; UA042.001.038.00011; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Tuition and Fees, 1988 -- 1989; UA042.001.038.00012; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Tuition and Fees HEDS, 1994 -- 1995; UA042.001.038.00013; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Tuition and Fees Chronicle of Higher Education, 1995; UA042.001.038.00014; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Tuition and Fees HEDS, 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.038.00015; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Tuitions- Fall, 1996 -- 1997; UA042.001.038.00016; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - HEDS Reports Issued Book 1, 1994; UA042.001.038.00017; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - HEDS Book 1 of 2 [1 of 2], 1994 -- 1995; UA042.001.038.00018; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - HEDS Book 1 of 2 [2 of 2], 1994 -- 1995; UA042.001.038.00019; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - HEDS Book 2 of 2 [1 of 3], 1994 -- 1995; UA042.001.038.00020; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - HEDS Book 2 of 2 [2 of 3], 1994 -- 1995; UA042.001.038.00021; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - HEDS Book 2 of 2 [3 of 3], 1994 -- 1995; UA042.001.038.00022; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Amazon Gift Certificate (FY04 Office), 2003 -- 2004; UA042.001.038.00023; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Office - C141100 - FY 04 - July (FY04 Office), 2003 -- 2004; UA042.001.038.00024; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Office - C141100 - FY 04 - August (FY04 Office), 2003 -- 2004; UA042.001.038.00025; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Office - C141100 - FY 04 - Oct (FY04 Office), 2003 -- 2004; UA042.001.038.00026; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Office - C141100 - FY 04 - Sept (FY04 Office), 2003 -- 2004; UA042.001.038.00027; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Office - C141100 - FY 04 - Nov (FY04 Office), 2003 -- 2004; UA042.001.038.00028; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Office - C141100 - FY 04 - Dec (FY04 Office), 2003 -- 2004; UA042.001.038.00029; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Office - C141100 - FY 04 - Jan (FY04 Office), 2003 -- 2004; UA042.001.038.00030; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Office - C141100 - FY 04 - Feb (FY04 Office), 2003 -- 2004; UA042.001.038.00031; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Office - C141100 - FY 04 - Mar (FY04 Office), 2003 -- 2004; UA042.001.038.00032; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Office - C141100 - FY 04 - Apr (FY04 Office), 2003 -- 2004; UA042.001.038.00033; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Office - C141100 - FY 04 - May (FY04 Office), 2003 -- 2004; UA042.001.038.00034; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Office - C141100 - FY 04 - June (FY04 Office), 2003 -- 2004; UA042.001.038.00035; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - FY04 PCard Trans, 2003 -- 2004; UA042.001.038.00036; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Research - C141200 - FY 04 - July (FY04 Research), 2003 -- 2004; UA042.001.038.00037; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Research - C141200 - FY 04 - August (FY04 Research), 2003 -- 2004; UA042.001.038.00038; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Research - C141200 - FY 04 - Sept (FY04 Research), 2003 -- 2004; UA042.001.038.00039; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Research - C141200 - FY 04 - Oct (FY04 Research), 2003 -- 2004; UA042.001.038.00040; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Research - C141200 - FY 04 - Nov (FY04 Research), 2003 -- 2004; UA042.001.038.00041; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Research - C141200 - FY 04 - Dec (FY04 Research), 2003 -- 2004; UA042.001.038.00042; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Research - C141200 - FY 04 - Jan (FY04 Research), 2003 -- 2004; UA042.001.038.00043; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Research - C141200 - FY 04 - Feb (FY04 Research), 2003 -- 2004; UA042.001.038.00044; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Research - C141200 - FY 04 - Mar (FY04 Research), 2003 -- 2004; UA042.001.038.00045; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Research - C141200 - FY 04 - April (FY04 Research), 2003 -- 2004; UA042.001.038.00046; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Research - C141200 - FY 04 - May (FY04 Research), 2003 -- 2004; UA042.001.038.00047; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - Research - C141200 - FY 04 - June (FY04 Research), 2003 -- 2004; UA042.001.038.00048; Office of Institutional Research (Box 38)
  - C141100 - FY05 July (Office FY05), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00001; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - C141100 - FY05 August (Office FY05), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00002; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - C141100 - FY05 September (Office FY05), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00003; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - C141100 - FY05 October (Office FY05), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00004; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - C141100 - FY05 November (Office FY05), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00005; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - C141100 - FY05 December (Office FY05), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00006; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - C141100 - FY05 January (Office FY05), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00007; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - C141100 - FY05 February (Office FY05), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00008; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - C141100 - FY05 March (Office FY05), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00009; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - C141100 - FY05 April (Office FY05), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00010; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - C141100 - FY05 May (Office FY05), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00011; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - C141100 - FY05 June (Office FY05), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00012; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - PCard Transactions - FY05 [1 of 2], 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00013; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - PCard Transactions - FY05 [2 of 2], 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00014; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - C141200 - FY05 - July (Research FY05), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00015; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - C141200 - FY05 - August (Research FY05), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00016; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - C141200 - FY05 - September (Research FY05), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00017; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - C141200 - FY05 - October (Research FY05), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00018; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - C141200 - FY05 - November (Research FY05), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00019; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - C141200 - FY05 - December (Research FY05), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00020; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - C141200 - FY05 - January (Research FY05), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00021; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - C141200 - FY05 - February (Research FY05), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00022; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - C141200 - FY05 - March (Research FY05), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00023; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - C141200 - FY05 - April (Research FY05), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00024; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - C141200 - FY05 - May (Research FY05), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00025; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - C141200 - FY05 - June (Research FY05), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00026; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - A (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00027; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - Board of Overseers 28 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00028; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - Bylaws of Trustees 23 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00029; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - Trustees 26 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00030; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - Administrative Committee 32 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00031; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - Administrative Organization 38 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00032; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - Dept Chairs/Program Chairs 42 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00033; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - Faculty Committees 45 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00034; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - Student Government 49 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00035; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - Research and Education Centers (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00036; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - Athletics 99 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00037; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - Degree Programs, Religious, Cultural and Special Interest Programs, Academic Resource Centers (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00038; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - Student Financial Aid 96 (& undergrad sel stats) (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00039; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - Grad and Undergrad Financial Income/Awards 95,96 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00040; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - Charact of Entering Class 79 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00041; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - SAT of Entering Class 75 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00042; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - Admissions Statistics 76 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00043; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - F-T and P-T Student Enrollment 81 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00044; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - F-T Students (program, sex, ethnic) 84 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00045; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - Intl Students By Country / Leading Country (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00046; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - Intl Students - Summer Eng Land Prog 88 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00047; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - Summer Session Enrollments 89 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00048; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - Student Faculty Ratio 90 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00049; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - Students by State / Territory (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00050; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - Graduating Seniors by Major (and 1,2,3) 100 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00051; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - College of Special Studies Enrollment 108 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00052; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - Tuition Rates 93 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00053; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - Undergrad Charges - Comparisons 94 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00054; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - Graduate Degrees Granted 104 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00055; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - Fact Book Edited Draft (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.039.00056; Office of Institutional Research (Box 39)
  - Paid Personnel 111 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00001; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Tenure/Tenure Eligible 118 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00002; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Ave. F-T Faculty Salary 120 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00003; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Intl Faculty/Scholars By Country 121 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00004; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Endowed and Term Chairs 122 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00005; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Paid Faculty Appointments 116 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00006; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Classrooms by Bldg/Usage (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00007; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Facilities by Room Type (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00008; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Area of Room Types by School/Div (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00009; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Residential Housing (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00010; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Libraries (Inclusive) (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00011; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Operating Budgets 147 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00012; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Endowment 156 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00013; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Accreditation (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00014; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Memberships p.162 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00015; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Medal Recipients 163 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00016; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Honorary Degrees Awarded 165 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00017; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Alum - Multiple Degree Holders 169 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00018; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Living Alum by Country 170 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00019; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Living Alum by State 172 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00020; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)